Guide to the UE Organizers Records, 1937-2003 UE.7.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Organizer Records, 7-3-1.
  - Meyer, Rachel: Organizer Reports, 1995-1999 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Miglino, Joseph, 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Millan, Edwin, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Miller, Arthur Lee, 1945-1948 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Miller, Brian, 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Miller, Joseph: Correspondence, 1967-1993 (Box 30, Folder 15-16)
  - Miller, Joseph: Organizer Reports, 1968-1969, 1980-1993 (Box 30, Folder 17-22)
  - Miller, Kenneth, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Miller, Mitchell: Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Miller, Mitchell: Organizer Reports, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 25-26)
  - Miller, Richard, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 27-28)
  - Miller, Steven, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Milton, Eve, 1951-1952 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Mintz, Robert, 1945-1946 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Mitchell, Daniel, 1988-1991 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Mitchell, John, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Mitchell, Michael: Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Mitchell, Michael: Organizer Reports, 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Molina, Oscar: Correspondence, 1978-1992 (Box 30, Folder 36-37)
  - Molina, Oscar: Organizer Reports, 1980-1982 (Box 31, Folder 01-04)
  - Moller, Kay, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Monroy, Valdemar, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Monteith, Ruth, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Montgomery, Jack, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Moody, William, 1952-1959 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Moore, Bardella, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Moore, Gilbert, 1976-1979 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Morin, Pamela: Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Morin, Pamela: Organizer Reports, 1981-1988 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Mott, Michael, 1976-1982 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Morton, Victor, 1952-1953 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Mouser, James, 1953-1954 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Moyer, Ernest, 1946-1955 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Mroz, Steve: Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Mroz, Steve: Organizer Reports, 1960-1964 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Muelver, Emil: Correspondence, 1953-1968 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Muelver, Emil: Organizer Reports, 1960-1967 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Mugford, Walter, 1939-1964 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Muhammad, Judith Ann, 1989-1992 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Murdock, William: Correspondence, 1949-1974 (Box 31, Folder 24-25)
  - Murdock, William: Organizer Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Myers, Jack, 1946-1948 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Neibur, Richard: Correspondence, 1940-1965 (Box 31, Folder 28-30)
  - Neibur, Richard: Correspondence, 1940-1965 (Box 32, Folder 01-03)
  - Neibur, Richard: Organizer Reports, 1949-1972 (Box 32, Folder 04-05)
  - Neil, Thomas, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Nelson, Harry: Correspondence, 1959-1976 (Box 32, Folder 07-08)
  - Nelson, Harry: Organizer Reports, 1959-1976 (Box 32, Folder 09-10)
  - Newell, Amy: Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 32, Folder 11-12)
  - Newell, Amy: Organizer Reports, 1980-1985 (Box 32, Folder 13-15)
  - Newell, Charles, 1937-1947 (Box 33, Folder 01-14)
  - Newton, Edward, 1946-1947 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Nichamin, Julie, 1978-1980 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Nichol, Herbert, 1948-1956 (Box 33, Folder 17-18)
  - Nieber, Richard, 1940-1947 (Box 33, Folder 19-25)
  - Nightingale, William, 1944-1946 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Nixon, Linda, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Noble, James: Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 33, Folder 28-29)
  - Noble, James: Organizer Reports, 1957-1964 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Noble, Larry, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Nordman, John, 1942-1947 (Box 33, Folder 32-33)
  - Noviscky, Michael, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Nydes, Jules, 1937-1939 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Ober, Bebe, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - O'Brien, Margaret, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - O'connor, Paul, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - O'Donald, Harry, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Ohler, Ruth, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Oleski, Edward, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - O'Laughlin, Robert, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - O'Malley, Thomas, 1951, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Onasch, William, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Orendain, Antonio, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Orozco, Benjamin, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Ostrow, Thelma, 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Outlaw, Joe, 1946-1947 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Overby, Elizabeth: Correspondence, 1942-1974 (Box 33, Folder 49-53)
  - Overby, Elizabeth: Correspondence, 1942-1974 (Box 34, Folder 01-04)
  - Overby, Elizabeth: Organizer Reports, 1956-1971 (Box 34, Folder 05-08)
  - Overby, William, 1953-1958 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Page, Rick, 1990-1992 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Palmer, David, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Palmer, Edward, 1943-1945 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Palmer, Fred, 1942-1943 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Palmer, Peter, 1967-1970 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Pantoja, Maria, 1991-1993 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Paradise, John, 1942-1953 (Box 34, Folder 16-17)
  - Parker, John, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Parks, Walter: Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Parks, Walter: Organizer Reports, 1995-1998 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Partee, Teresa, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Partyka, Eric, 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Pascale, John, 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Pasche, Victor, 1944-1952 (Box 34, Folder 24-25)
  - Pascoe, James, 1936-1942 (Box 34, Folder 26-33)
  - Pascoe, James, 1936-1942 (Box 35, Folder 01-16)
  - Patterson, James, 1947-1949 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Patterson, Maxine, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Payne, Bessie, 1949-1953 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Payne, Elliot, 1946-1949 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Payne, Forest: Correspondence, 1942-1964 (Box 35, Folder 21-22)
  - Payne, Forest: Organizer Reports, 1950-1954 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Payne, James, 1940-1950 (Box 35, Folder 24-29)
  - Pelletier, Hilda, 1943-1949 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Perillo, Vincent, 1949-1950 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Perkey, Margaret, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Perkins, Charles, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Perkins, Haven, 1943-1948 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Perry, Douglas: Correspondence, 1948-1987 (Box 35, Folder 35-38)
  - Perry, Douglas: Organizer Reports, 1965-1981 (Box 35, Folder 39-40)
  - Persily, Joseph: Correspondence, 1941-1956 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Persily, Joseph: Organizer Reports, 1949-1955 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Petanovich, Mike, 1937-1938 (Box 36, Folder 03-05)
  - Peters, Charles, 1944-1950 (Box 36, Folder 06-07)
  - Petit-Clair, Alfred, 1949-1950 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Petrucelli, Josephine, 1942-1943 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Pharis, Clyde, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Phillips, Denzel, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Phillips, Mildred, 1948-1950 (Box 36, Folder 12-13)
  - Pierce, Homer, 1942-1945 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Pifer, Dorothy, 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Pinkston, Don, 1942-1949 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Pinter, John, 1944-1945 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Plataky, Joseph, 1949-1957 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Plavsity, Milan, 1967-1969 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Podell, Wilma (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Pogue, Donald, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Poirier, John, 1944 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Polaski, Sandra: Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Polaski, Sandra: Organizer Reports, 1976-1984 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Pollack, Ernest, 1941-1943 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Pologruto, Paul: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Pologruto, Paul: Organizer Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Poritz, Harold, 1952-1955 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Portiz, Harold, 1952-1955 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Portnoy, Murray, 1946-1948 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Potegal, Leo, 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Potegal, Sol, 1949-1952 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Powell, Robert, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Prather, J. Gilbert, 1942-1943 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Prinkey, Raymond, 1975-1977 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Prose, Jeremy, 1998-2000 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Quinn, Thomas: Correspondence, 1949-1968 (Box 36, Folder 37-39)
  - Quinn, Thomas: Organizer Reports, 1954-1972 (Box 36, Folder 40-41)
  - Raben, William, 1942-1944 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Radosevich, Emil, 1946-1948 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Raitano, Arthur, 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Raleigh, Eugene, 1945-1946 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Raley, Talmage, 1941-1952 (Box 36, Folder 46-47)
  - Ralph, Elmer, 1951-1955 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Ramirez, Ruth: Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Ramirez, Ruth: Organizer Reports, 1977-1986 (Box 36, Folder 51-52)
  - Randall, Equhart, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Ratner, David (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Real, Clayton, 1947-1950 (Box 37, Folder 03-04)
  - Reardon, Joseph, 1978-1982 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Reed, Marie, 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Reed, Rick: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Reed, Rick: Organizer Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Regan, Larry, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Reiff, Donald, 1937-1938 (Box 37, Folder 10-11)
  - Reno, Walter, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Repaal, Magne, 1944-1945 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Rexrode, Roy, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Reyes, Cesar, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Reynolds, Robert, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Rhine, Henry: Correspondence, 1942-1955 (Box 37, Folder 17-25)
  - Rhine, Jessica, 1943-1945 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Rice, Robert, 1942-1955 (Box 37, Folder 27-31)
  - Richards, Ed, 1942-1943 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Ricker, Todd: Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Ricker, Todd: Organizer Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Riedlinger, Wesley: Organizer Reports, 1963-1977 (Box 37, Folder 35-36)
  - Riegal, Edward, 1942-1943 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Riffle, Robert, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Riker, Willard, 1941-1948 (Box 37, Folder 39-41)
  - Riley, Jeffrey, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Riley, Sylvan, 1951-1955 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Riordan, Ray, 1999-2001 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Riskin, Benjamin, 1943-1956 (Box 37, Folder 46-49)
  - Rittenhouse, Jack, 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Ritter, Connie: Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Ritter, Connie: Organizer Reports, 1990-1994 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Rivers, Charles, 1937-1951 (Box 38, Folder 01-23)
  - Robbins, William, 1943-1944 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Roberto, Dione, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Roberts, Justin, 1943 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Roberts, Kent: Correspondence, 1957-1969 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Roberts, Kent: Organizer Reports, 1964-1969 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Roberts, Thomas, 1941-1943 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Roberts, William, 1942 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Robinson, Frank, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Robinson (Sparks), Irene, 1943-1944 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Robinson, Lee, 1952-1954 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Robinson, Paul, 1946-1947 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Rodgers, Frank, 1942-1946 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Rodgers, Margaret, 1946-1948 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Rodrigues, Anthony, 1949-1956 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Rodriguez, Anthony, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Rodriguez, Horacio: Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Rodriguez, Horacio: Organizer Reports, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Rodriguez, Jacobo, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Rodriguez, Javier, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Rodriguez, Salvador, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Romeo, Vincent, 1943-1948 (Box 38, Folder 44-45)
  - Romer, Joseph, 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Rooney, George, 1943-1950 (Box 38, Folder 47-48)
  - Roose, Edgar, 1942-1946 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Rose, Alice, 1946-1948 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Rose, Syd, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - Rosen, Frank: Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 52-54)
  - Rosen, Frank: Organizer Reports, 1966-1973 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - Rosene, William, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Rosner, Steve, 1949-1950 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Ross (West), Ann, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Ross, Manae, 2001-2003 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Rossetti, Timothy: Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Rossetti, Timothy: Organizer Reports, 1986-1990 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Royce, Pauline, 1948-1952 (Box 39, Folder 07-08)
  - Rubin, Larry, 1969-1976 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Rubens, William, 1950-1951 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Rudich, Stephen, 1947-1950 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Ruff, Judith, 1978-1980 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Rumley, James: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Rumley, James: Organizer Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Rusak, Jack, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Russo, Joseph, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Rust, Gilbert, 1942-1943 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Rutledge, James: Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Rutledge, James: Organizer Reports, 1976-1980 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Ruzansky, Abraham, 1947, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Ryan, Athene, 1942-1943 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Ryan, Lawrence, 1945-1954 (Box 39, Folder 22-23)
  - Saba, David (Philip), 1945-1956 (Box 39, Folder 24-26)
  - Sack (Neider), Mildred, 1946-1947 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Sackter, Viola, 1944-19467 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Sage, Lambert, 1945-1947 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Saggio, Peter, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Salese, Anthony, 1948-1953 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Salkind, Isadore, 1948-1949 (Box 39, Folder 32-33)
  - Salter, Herbert, 1948-1950 (Box 39, Folder 34-35)
  - Sanders, William, 1989-1990 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Sanderson, Raymond, 1951-1952 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Sanneman, William, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Santora, William, 1941-1956 (Box 39, Folder 39-42)
  - Sardo, Alba, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Sarti, Louis, 1938-1950 (Box 39, Folder 44-50)
  - Sartisky, Jack, 1947-1951 (Box 39, Folder 51-52)
  - Saunders, Clifford, 1941-1956 (Box 39, Folder 53-55)
  - Saunders, George, 1942-1943 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - Sayer, Michael, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - Saylor, Frances, 1945-1950 (Box 39, Folder 58-59)
  - Scheiner, Frank, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Schestok, Gustau: Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Schestok, Gustau: Organizer Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Schlenker, Kathryn: Correspondence, 1956-1982 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Schlenker, Kathryn: Organizer Reports, 1956-1971 (Box 40, Folder 03-05)
  - Schlipf, Paul, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Schmidt, Russell, 1942-1943 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Schmidt (Kaplan), Roth, 1942-1943 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Schneider, Gregory: Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Schneider, Gregory: Organizer Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Schubert, Jack, 1938-1941 (Box 40, Folder 11-15)
  - Schwaner, Barbara, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Schwartz, Jonathan, 1965-1967 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Schwenkmeyer, Frieda, 1955-1956 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Scifano, Anthony, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Scott, Helen, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Scott, Walter, 1936-1940 (Box 40, Folder 21-23)
  - Self, Davis, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Sentner, William: Correspondence, 1948-1958 (Box 40, Folder 25-28)
  - Sentner, William: Organizer Reports, 1950-1953 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Serna, Reuben, 1981-1985 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Shade, Larry, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Shaffer, John, 1949-1954 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Sharkey, Thomas, 1971-1973 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Sharp, Joan, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Sharpley, Dannette, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Shea, Kathleen: Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Shea, Kathleen: Organizer Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Shield, James, 1950-1955 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Sheehan, William, 1948-1955 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Selman, Nathan, 1948-1950 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Siakasone, Khonsavanh, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Siler, William, 1949-1950 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Silvia, Frank, 1948-1950 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Silver, Roberta: Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Silver, Roberta: Organizer Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Silver, William, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Silverstein, Joseph, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Simon, Robert, 1955-1957 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Slagle, Laverne, 1948-1952 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Sliva, Frank, 1949-1950 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Sloth, Michael, 1984-1987 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Albert J. Jr.: Correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Albert J. Jr.: Organizer Reports, 1991-1997 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Albert L., 1948-1965 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Smith, Alfred, 1951-1955 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Smith, Alice, 1940-1955 (Box 41, Folder 24-26)
  - Smith, Daniel: Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Smith, Daniel: Organizer Reports, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Hilliard, 1938-1939 (Box 41, Folder 29-30)
  - Smith, John K., 1944-1945 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Smith, John M., 1936-1938 (Box 41, Folder 32-33)
  - Smith, Owen, 1941-1948 (Box 41, Folder 34-37)
  - Smith, Philip, 1943-1950 (Box 41, Folder 38-42)
  - Smith, Robert, 1945-1946 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Smith, Sara, 1951-1955 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Smith, William, 1943-1956 (Box 42, Folder 02-03)
  - Smith, W.F., 1937 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Smorodin, Ted, 1948-1950 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Smucker, Samuel: Correspondence, 1995-2001 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Smucker, Samuel: Organizer Reports, 1995-2001 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Snider, Charles D., 1944-1947 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Snow, Fred, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Soda, Penny, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Solorzano, Marty: Correspondence, 1988-1996 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Solorzano, Marty: Organizer Reports, 1989-1992 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Sommer, Rebecca, 1989-1991 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Sommers, Stephen, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Sonnycalb, Margaret, 1943-1945 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Sparrow, Marvin, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Spector, Harriet, 1942-1943 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Spinnate, Anthony, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Spinozzi, Connie, 1993-1997 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Springer, Barbara, 1943-1945 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Squires, Joseph, 1943-1955 (Box 42, Folder 21-22)
  - Sramek, Martin, 1943-1944 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Staas, Ozro, 1947-1950 (Box 42, Folder 24-25)
  - Staber, Alexander, 1949-1950 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Staff, Leroy, 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Stager, Waldo, 1940-1954 (Box 42, Folder 28-36)
  - Stalbird, Richard, 1946-1947 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Stamper, John, 1946-1949 (Box 42, Folder 38-39)
  - Stanton, Arnold, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Starvus (Silver), Loretta, 1943-1946 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - States, Robert, 1984-1988 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Steele, Lillie, 1944-1948 (Box 42, Folder 43-44)
  - Steeley, William Jr., 1951-1954 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Steffens, Dorothy, 1944-1946 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Steinberg, Gerald: Correspondence, 1943-1978 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Steinberg, Gerald: Organizer Reports, 1943-1948, 1963-1970 (Box 42, Folder 48-50)
  - Steinberger, Willis, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Steiner, Charles, 1953-1957 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Stensky, Joseph, 1948-1950 (Box 42, Folder 53-55)
  - Stevens, George: Correspondence, 1963-1997 (Box 43, Folder 01-03)
  - Stevens, George: Organizer Reports, 1964-1997 (Box 43, Folder 04-10)
  - Stevens, Ruth, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Stevenson, Joseph, 1965-1967 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Steward, Warren, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Stone, Judith, 1944-1945 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Stoner, Wayne, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Stonkus, Albert, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Stover, Beryl, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Stover, Fred (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Strasburg, Ray, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Strickland, Clyde, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Strong, Eric, 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Studant, Frank, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Sturgen, Richard, 1989-1992 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Suber, Thomas, 1994-1996 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Surace, Frank: Correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Surace, Frank: Organizer Reports, 1964-1969 (Box 43, Folder 26-27)
  - Swan, Elvis, 1943-1962 (Box 43, Folder 28-30)
  - Swanson, Sam, 1941-1943 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Sweat, Mary, 1942-1944 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Sweet, Joseph, 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Tabb, Barbara, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Tague, Hugh: Correspondence, 1976-1984 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Tague, Hugh: Organizer Reports, 1977-1983 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Tangredi, Caroline, 1943-1944 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Tapper, Owen: Correspondence, 1957-1963 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Tapper, Owen: Organizer Reports, 1952-1961 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Taragos, William, 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Tatham, Michael, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, Barnard, 1947-1950 (Box 44, Folder 07-08)
  - Taylor, Coleman, 1936-1937 (Box 44, Folder 09-11)
  - Taylor, Donald: Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Taylor, Donald: Organizer Reports, 1996-1999 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Taylor, Sidney, 1937 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Tehle, Mark, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Teto, William, 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Thamel, Vassel: Correspondence, 1947-1956 (Box 44, Folder 17-18)
  - Thamel, Vassel: Organizer Reports, 1949-1956 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Thoma, Steve, 1942-1944 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Thomas, Irene, 1987-1991 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Thomas, John, 1941-1946 (Box 44, Folder 22-24)
  - Thomas, Ronald, 1974-1976 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Thompson, Ernest, 1943-1956 (Box 44, Folder 26-27)
  - Thompson, George, 1945-1946 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Thompson, Olive, 1949-1950 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Tice, Esther, 1944-1952 (Box 44, Folder 30-32)
  - Tillow, Walter, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Timms, Raymond, 1944-1947 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Titleman, Leonard, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Tobler, James, 1999-2001 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Tomassetti, Nicholas: Correspondence, 1942-1978 (Box 44, Folder 37-40)
  - Tomassetti, Nicholas: Organizer Reports, 1949-1970 (Box 44, Folder 41-42)
  - Tomassetti, Nicholas: Organizer Reports, 1971-1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Tormey, Donald: Correspondence, 1941-1979 (Box 45, Folder 02-13)
  - Tormey, Donald: Organizer Reports, 1950-1984 (Box 45, Folder 14-16)
  - Tormey, Michael, 1974-1976 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Tormey, Stephen: Correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Tormey, Stephen: Organizer Reports, 1973-1979 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Torre, Louis: Correspondence, 1936-1954 (Box 45, Folder 20-26)
  - Torre, Louis: Organizer Reports, 1949-1951 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Toth, John, 1964-1972 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Townsend, Richard, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Treffman, Mildred, 1943-1944 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Tries, Bette, 1951-1952 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Trinh, Sissy, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Tripp, Andrew, 1999-2001 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Trout, Melvin, 1952-1957 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Turkowski, Joseph, 1944-1977 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Turner, Leo: Correspondence, 1937-1950 (Box 46, Folder 09-43)
  - Turner, Leo: Organizer Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Unger, Henry: Correspondence, 1974-1982 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Unger, Henry: Organizer Reports, 1975-1982 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Urba, Frances, 1945-1946 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Valenzuela, Luis, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Van Dycke, Lloyd, 1945-1947 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Van Gelder, Philip: Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 47, Folder 06-09)
  - Van Hove, Jeffrey, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Van Howe, Otto, 1947-1948 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Van Tyne, Claude: Correspondence, 1942-1979 (Box 47, Folder 12-17)
  - Van Tyne, Claude: Organizer Reports, 1956-1967 (Box 47, Folder 18-19)
  - Van Wagenen, Jared: Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Van Wagenen, Jared: Organizer Reports, 1976-1979 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Vance, Peggy, 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Velleman, Leonard, 1945-1948 (Box 47, Folder 23-24)
  - Verin, Olga, 1946-1947 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Verri, Albert, 1949-1955 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Villano, Louis, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Villarreal, Gabriel: Correspondence, 1970-1981 (Box 47, Folder 28)